(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T22:19:21.228919",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
高鳴る心臓に祈りを乗せて
Sending a prayer through my throbbing heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
I paint an ambiguous dream.
幻想は想像のまま
Even if the fantasy remains a mere imagination,
終われないんだ
it cannot end here!
みんな！今日見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to see me today!
答えを延々と探し続けて
Endlessly searching for the answer,
何者かになりたくて
wanting to become someone.
潸々と降る夕立を
The evening shower pouring heavily...
ただ眺めた
I just stared at it.
優しく寄り添って
Gently staying close,
心が晴れるのなら
if it could clear my heart,
翼が生えたような気がして
I feel as if I've grown wings,
いつだって隣にいるから
because I will always be by your side.
だって言葉紡いで唄うことが
For weaving words to sing
わたしの運命だ
is my destiny.
世界にありふれた虚しささえも
Overwriting even the emptiness
上書きして
common in this world,
路地裏に咲いた花のように
like a flower blooming in a back alley,
願いを照らす
illuminating my wish.
小さな光に憧れて
Yearning for a small light...
名前を持たない歌なんて
A song without a name,
神様は認めてくれない
God will never acknowledge it.
一つ一つ枯れない花のように
Like flowers, one by one, that never wither.
昨日の自分にさよなりして
Saying goodbye to my yesterday self,
こぼれた涙
as my tears overflow.
うまく笑えなくてもいいかな
Is it okay if I can't smile well?
だって理想は遠ざかっていくばかり
Because ideals keep getting further away,
もう散々だよ
I'm so sick of it.
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって
No matter how much I reach out and scream,
届かないの
it doesn't reach.
望めばいつか叶うはずって
Believing that if I wish for it,
信じている
it will come true someday.
どうか歌よ響いて
Please, oh song, resound!
あぁ心臓の鼓動が今日も
Ah, the beating of my heart today, too,
うるさい
is so loud.
留まれば足がすくんで立ってないよ
If I stop, my legs will freeze and I won't be able to stand.
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出すんだ
I'll find you and pull you out from this soundless world.
言葉紡いで歌うことが私の運命だ
Spinning words and singing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the emptiness common in this world,
路地裏に咲いた花のように迷い人照らす
I will light the path for the lost, like a flower blooming in a back alley.
小さな光
With a tiny light...
に憧れて
...that I yearn for.
君の歌姫になれたかな いいな
I wonder if I managed to become your diva... I hope so.
okey dokey 返事はいいけど 冗談なら笑えないよ
Okey dokey, your reply is fine, but I can't laugh if it's a joke.
渋滞曖昧どっちを向いちゃうの 蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
Traffic jam, ambiguity, which way are you looking? I reached out my hand to a mirage.
微熱のような夢物語 そんな光は見ない振りしていた
A dream-like story resembling a slight fever, I was pretending not to see such a light.
ざわめく鼓動まだ行かないで
Throbbing heartbeat, don't go yet.
幻じゃ嫌だよ 私を奪って
I don't want it to be an illusion, steal me away.
魅惑の斬新な支配
Fascinating, novel control...
広がって収まんない universe
...expanding into an uncontrollable universe.
君の表情は私の森羅万象を 書き換えちゃうかも責任重大ね
Your expression might rewrite all of existence to me, such heavy responsibility, right?
一切合切 dance dance dance we are dancing reed
All-inclusive, dance dance dance, we are dancing reed.
夢中になって絡み合ったゼログラビティ
Got engrossed and intertwined in zero gravity.
構わず dance dance dance just a dance just a dance
Without caring, dance dance dance, just a dance, just a dance.
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice entrusted to the darkness...
目を覚ましても離れないで
...even after waking up, don't leave me.
maybe needy 正気じゃないのよ 体温が忘れられない
Maybe needy, I'm out of my mind, I can't forget your body temperature.
誰彼そんなんじゃないから 独り占めして euphoria
It's not like that with just anyone, hogging you all to myself, euphoria.
気にしてない様な言葉は装飾で メイクの様には流せない
Words that seem nonchalant are just decoration, you can't wash them away like makeup.
360度偽りだって 隠しきれぬような
Even 360-degree falsehoods cannot be fully hidden...
私に構って嬉しいなんて crazy crazy love
...being happy that you pay attention to me, crazy crazy love.
摩天楼から連れ去って
Carry me away from the skyscraper.
君の表情は私の深層心理を
Your expression swaps my deep subconscious...
すり替えちゃうのよ責任重大ね
...such heavy responsibility, right?
過ぎ去ったネオン 残像 shooting star
Passed neon, afterimage shooting star.
グライダーみたいに漂えば 幸も不幸もなかった
If I drift like a glider, there was neither happiness nor unhappiness.
指先でまた君を探している その声を聴かせてよ
Searching for you again with my fingertips, let me hear that voice.
私に構って 教えてよ恋の先を！
Pay attention to me, tell me what lies beyond love!
広がって収まんない universe
Expanding, uncontrollable universe.
君の存在は私の将来までも 踏み込んだのよ付き合ってよね
Your existence even stepped into my future, go out with me, won't you?
一切合切 dance dance dance we are dancing reed
All-inclusive, dance dance dance, we are dancing reed.
夢中になって絡み合ったゼログラビティ
Got engrossed and intertwined in zero gravity.
構わず dance dance dance just a dance just a dance
Without caring, dance dance dance, just a dance, just a dance.
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice entrusted to the darkness...
目を覚ましても離れないで
...even after waking up, don't leave me.
みんな！今日は誕生日ライブに来てくれて、ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to my birthday live stream today!
コメントも見えているよ！
I can see your comments too!
最初に聴いてもらったのが『Diva』『Dancing Reed』でした！
The first two songs you heard were "Diva" and "Dancing Reed"!
この二つの曲は、あの、フェスと、あと去年のね、ドラマの主題歌に使っていただいた曲で
These two songs, well, they were used for the festival and as the theme song for last year's drama...
すごく思い出に残っているので、最初に二曲歌ってみようかなと思って選びました！
...and since they bring back so many memories, I chose to sing them first!
そして、今回はですね、ときのそらお披露目誕生日 2026...
And this time, it's "Tokino Sora Debut Birthday 2026"...
ときのそらおじゃないよ、ときのそらだよ！
It's not "Tokino Sora-o", it's "Tokino Sora"!
ええ、みんなの呟きを待ってるので、
Yes, I'm waiting for everyone's tweets, so...
たくさん呟いてほしいな！
...I hope you'll tweet a lot!
トレンド入るといいな！
It would be great if it trended!
ねー！
Right?
そして、今回のテーマは、8周年を象徴する
And the theme this time, symbolizing our 8th anniversary...
無限をモチーフに、宇宙や星をステージに散りばめて、
...uses infinity as a motif, with space and stars scattered on stage...
中毒性のあるビート、リズムの曲で絡めた、デジタルパルスライブです！
...and combined with addictive beats and rhythms, it's the Digital Pulse Live!
デジタルパルスライブです！
The Digital Pulse Live!
こちらね、大きな天球が曲によってどう変わるのかを見ていてください
Please watch how this large armillary sphere changes with each song.
そしてね、今年ののんのんは、ええ、5つなので、
Also, this year there are five Non-nons, so...
くるくる回転してます。くるくるくるくるくるくる…
...they're spinning around and around...
そして、夜空にはソラザウルスもいるよ！
And Sorasaurus is also in the night sky!
ソラザウルスはね、なんとね、炎を出せるようになりました
Believe it or not, Sorasaurus is now able to breathe fire!
ぷしゅー！
Whoosh!
あんきももね、ちゃんとあんきもザウルス？もあるんですけど、見えるかな？
We also have Ankimo-saurus as well, can you see it?
もちろん、あと、今年も新衣装のお披露目や、告知したゲストと、
Of course, we also have the new outfit reveal, the announced guests...
ええ、あと、どんな曲を披露するのかを楽しみにしててくださいね！
...and what kind of songs we'll perform, so please look forward to it!
そして、次に行く前に、プチお披露目、最初にしちゃいましょう！
And before we move on, let's start with a mini-reveal!
カメラさん、上を向いてください！
Camera person, please look up!
はい！というわけで、新しいお団子ヘア！新髪型お披露目です！
Yes! So here it is, the new double bun hair! My new hairstyle reveal!
それでは早速ゲストパートにいってみよう。可愛いありがとう！おお可愛いありがとう！
Now let's go straight to the guest part. Thank you for the "cute" comments! Oh, thank you so much!
シロ組さんもいっぱいコメントしててね！
Shirogumi fans, please write lots of comments too!
最初のゲストは、この人です！
And our first guest is... this person!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
[Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026]
GUEST 電脳少女シロ
[Guest: Dennou Shojo Shiro]
星降るたびに
Every time stars fall,
恋をするたびに
every time we fall in love,
バイバイだって 夜はギャラクティカ
bye-bye, because the night is a galactica.
明星ギャラクティカ
[Song: Morning Star Galactica]
今夜は宇宙のアイオライトが
Tonight, the iolite of outer space...
いやに眩しいから
...is dazzlingly bright.
街のネオンからも星宿り
Let's escape from the neon lights of the town...
どこか逃げようか ふたり
...and find somewhere to stay among the stars, the two of us.
しどけないくらい 揺らぐグラスが
Because the swaying glass, so disorderly...
心惑わすから
...perplexes my heart.
あなただけ
Only you,
君だけ
only you,
今夜だけ
only tonight,
夜に星梯子掛ける
building a star ladder into the night.
見つめ
Looking at...
あなたの表情
...your expression,
照らして明星ギャラクティカ
illuminating the morning star galactica.
見上げた
Looking up,
あなたの瞳が
your eyes and...
宇宙がキラキラって光る
...the universe are sparkling.
近付く
As we get...
ほどにホードン
...closer, hold on.
ねえ 孤独ごと抱きしめて
Hey, embrace even the loneliness.
ふたりの銀河で手と手が星と星が
In our galaxy, hand in hand, star and star intersecting,
交わって恋はギャラクティカ
love is galactica.
パッ パッパー ヤ パッパ パッパー ヤ
Pap pappa-ya pappa pa pa-ya
嗚呼 同じペースで泳ぎだすペイヴメント
Ah, swimming out onto the pavement at the same pace,
宵と宵で繋ぐ朝へ 一度きりのラブ<
connecting evenings to morning with a once-in-a-lifetime love.
あなたとわたしの灯す星の行方は
Where did the stars we light point,
何光年先を指した？
how many light-years away?
結ぶオリオンの愛の星が
Because Orion's star of love, binding us together,
真っ赤に燃えるから
burns bright red.
今夜だけ
Only tonight,
君だけ
only you,
踊りましょう
let's dance,
夜は天の邪鬼だから
because the night is a mischievous spirit.
見つめ
Looking at...
あなたの表情
...your expression,
隠して明星ギャラクティカ
hiding the morning star galactica.
そのときめいた気持ちが未知だって
Even if that throbbing feeling is unknown,
手探りでいいから
groping in the dark is fine.
生まれたままの衝動
Hide the impulse just as you were born,
隠して明星ギャラクティカ
morning star galactica.
わたしの
My heartbeat,
あなたの
your heartbeat,
鼓動が 鼓動が ドキドキって疾る
racing with a thump-thump.
壊れる
As it feels like...
ほどにホードン
...breaking, hold on.
本当のこと言わないで
Don't tell me the truth.
最後の夜明けは手と手が星と星が
At the final dawn, hand in hand, star and star parting ways,
ほどけて君はギャラクティカ
you are galactica.
いつだって愛はロマンティカ
Love is always romántica.
はい！というわけで最初のゲストは…
Yes! And so, our first guest is...
シロちゃんだよ！
Shiro-chan!
こんにちは！ときの…
Hello! Tokino...
シロです！
Shiro!
シロ、ときのシロになっちゃった！
You became "Tokino Shiro"!
本当に今日は、そらちゃん…
Really, today, Sora-chan...
お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
すごいね、格好！
That outfit is amazing!
あ、あ、そらちゃんという歌姫にお会いできると聞いて…
Ah, hearing I could meet a diva like Sora-chan...
出せるものは全部出していこうと思います。
I thought I'd show everything I have.
そ、そういうことだったんだ。
S-So that's what it was.
待って、これチャンネルBANしちゃったら…
Wait, if this gets the channel banned...
そんなことない！大丈夫、大丈夫だから。
No way! It's okay, it's fine!
ごめんなさい。
I'm sorry.
胸が苦しくなってきました。
My chest is starting to hurt...
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
そらちゃん、クラゲさんには…
Sora-chan, I hear jellyfish...
毒針があると聞きます。
have poison stingers.
毒針をぜひ、頭でごちゅんと後ろに刺していただけませんか？
Could you please sting me with your head from behind?
え？…ごちゅん！
Eh? ...Sting!
ううっ、ううっ…
Ugh, ugh...
倒れる、倒れちゃう！
You're falling, you're gonna fall!
すごい、効いてきました！
Wow, it's really taking effect!
効いてきた？
Taking effect?
皆さん、そらちゃんは…
Everyone, Sora-chan...
変わりました。毒針を持った女に変わったんです！
has changed. She turned into a woman with a poison stinger!
ええ？そう、私強くなったから！
Eh? Yeah, because I became stronger!
そらちゃんは毒針が持ちたくて、可愛いクラゲヘアになったんですか？
Did you get cute jellyfish hair because you wanted a poison stinger, Sora-chan?
違う、違う、違う！私はやっぱり、アイドルといえばこういう可愛い髪型の人が多いかなと思って…
No, no, no! I thought, since many idols have cute hairstyles like this...
そういうアイドルっぽい髪型にしたいなと思ってたんだよね。
I wanted to go with an idol-like hairstyle.
そらちゃん、聞いてください。
Sora-chan, listen to me.
私もアイドルでしかないし、歌姫でしかないのに…
Even though I'm also just an idol and a diva...
ディーバっていう曲もあるんですけど、今もう…
I even have a song called "Diva," but now...
アイドルであろうと、なんかこう…なってるのに…
even though I'm trying to be an idol, I'm... like this...
努力してくれる姿がもう大好きで、食べたいくらい！
I just love how hard you work, I want to eat you up!
食べちゃうの？
Are you going to eat me?
シナモロールみたいですね。
You're like Cinnamoroll.
見て！カメラさん、見て見て！
Look! Mr. Cameraman, look, look!
シナモロール！
Cinnamoroll!
これはシナモロール、食べられちゃう、食べられちゃう…
This is Cinnamoroll being eaten, being eaten...
はい、ということで！
Yes, so!
はい、今日はBANされない発言を心がけていきます！
Yes, today I'll make sure to speak in a way that won't get us banned!
もうすでに結構シロちゃんワールド炸裂してますけど。
Although the Shiro-chan World has already exploded quite a bit.
あの、なんかこんな、大好きなそらちゃんのこんな場に…
Um, to be in a place like this with my beloved Sora-chan...
そらともさんたちと一緒に呼んでもらえると思わなくて…
I didn't think I'd be invited here along with all the Soratomos...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
3年ぶりだよね？
It's been three years, right?
あ！
Ah!
3年ぶりの元カノです。
I'm the ex-girlfriend of three years.
元カノじゃない！
Not ex-girlfriend!
そらともさん、一緒に、一緒に…
Soratomos, together, together...
独り占めしないので、愛でていきましょう！
I won't keep her all to myself, so let's adore her together!
今日はそらともさんに、シロの来た意味を分からせたいと思います。
Today, I want to show the Soratomos why Shiro came here.
そらちゃん、立ってください。
Sora-chan, please stand up.
はい！
Yes!
３、２、１…
Three, two, one...
バニーガールズ！
Bunny girls!
このスクショでいいの？ねえ？
Is this screenshot okay? Hey?
千手観音、千手観音。
Thousand-Handed Kannon, Thousand-Handed Kannon.
そらちゃん、新衣装のバニー衣装プレゼントしに来ました。
Sora-chan, I came to present you with a new bunny outfit.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
どうですか？
How is it?
可愛い！バニーガールも可愛いよ！
Cute! The bunny girl is cute too!
ウサギさんって万年発情してるので、ちょっとはぁはぁしてもらう…
Rabbits are in heat all year round, so could you pant a bit...
可愛い！
Cute!
あ、私の尻尾あるよ！
Ah, I have a tail too!
あ、そうだ！そらちゃんと言えば…
Ah, that's right! Speaking of Sora-chan...
尻尾を、ちょっと…
The tail, just a bit...
お触りしてもいいですか？
May I touch it?
いいよ！
Sure!
あ、大変！
Ah, oh no!
何？
What?
シロ、発情が止まらないので…
Shiro's heat won't stop, so...
そろそろお家に帰ります！
I should head home soon!
帰っちゃうの？
You're leaving?
はい！月からみんなを見守っています！このあとも楽しんで！
Yes! I'll watch over everyone from the moon! Keep having fun after this!
楽しんで！ありがとう！
Have fun! Thank you!
ちょっと、帰れてないよ！
Wait, you haven't fully left!
シロちゃんワールド炸裂で、楽しかったね。
The Shiro-chan World exploded, that was fun.
「なんだこれ」って言わないで、みんな！ねえ？
Don't say "What was that", everyone! Right?
でも、相変わらずのシロちゃんで、私、一緒にいられてとっても楽しかったです。
But, as always with Shiro-chan, I had so much fun being together.
マイペースだね、ねえ、マイペースだよ。私もマイペースだから、良いコンビってことだ！
She's very my-paced, right? She is. I am too, so that makes us a good duo!
というわけで、続いてのゲストに行きましょう！この人です！
And with that, let's move on to the next guest! Here they are!
全部全部アンタのせいだ
It's all, all your fault.
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
It's so annoying it makes me want to throw up.
何かに縋って 諛って
Clinging to something, playing the flatterer...
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
I was an idiot for expecting anything from you.
ご機嫌伺いの八方美人
An all-around crowd-pleaser, buttering everyone up,
それ故にアンチな一生 gimme
which is why you get a lifetime of haters, gimme.
浅いキャパシティ まいどおおきに
A shallow capacity, thank you as always,
詰まるところ人生ずっと地味
in short, your life is forever plain.
「憎たらしい！」「痛々しい！」
"Detestable!" "Pathetic!"
無視出来ないのが一層
Not being able to ignore it makes it even worse.
腹立たしい 苛立たしい
It's infuriating, it's irritating,
そろそろ飽きた自己満足に
I'm getting sick of your self-satisfaction.
ライクの反対はアパシー
The opposite of like is apathy...
≒繋がれた証
≒The proof of our connection.
切り離せない関係
An inseparable relationship,
逸らしてしまいたいわ
I just want to look away.
これは所謂ヘイトスピーチ
This is what they call hate speech,
匿名性の声明を生命に載せてんだ
placing anonymous declarations onto life itself.
鳴り止まないサイレン
An unending siren,
近づく度に痙攣
spasming every time it gets closer,
赤信号にずっと従順です
always obedient to the red light.
大体アナタのコト アタシ
Generally, when it comes to you, I...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キラ イ
really, really, really hate you!
omg 情けない 最早
Oh my god, so pathetic, at this point,
バイバイバイ バイバイしたい
I want to say bye-bye-bye, bye-bye.
脳内も 予測不能 故に
Inside my brain is unpredictable too, so,
解解 解 解解は 無い
there is no, no, no solution.
どうだい？ アタシのコト アナタ
How about it? When it comes to me, do you...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライになった？
really, really, really hate me now?
あぁ 百害あって一利ナシ
Ah, there are a hundred harms and not a single benefit,
nothing not see もしタラレバ
nothing, not see, even with "what ifs,"
並べてもニコチンだし
lining them up is just like nicotine.
i miss youって近付いた
Approaching with an "I miss you,"
結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
the ending was a clumsy mistake, a clumsy mistake.
センキュー 反面教師
Thank you, my negative role model,
後味一生消えてくんないわ
this aftertaste will never go away for the rest of my life.
よしよし いい子ね
Good, good, you're a good child,
笑顔 振り撒き パラパラ いい子ね
showering smiles, flake by flake, a good child.
だけど だけど その本性は？
But, but, what is your true nature?
善悪の区別も付かないの？ 笑
Can't you even tell good from bad? Haha.
減点方式で取り巻く環境に巻かれて
Swept up in a deducting-points environment,
生涯 痛い！痛い！痛い！も聞かれないわ！って
saying, "I won't even hear your pain, pain, pain for life!"
自然の報いにクラっちゃった
and getting hit by the natural consequences.
人は鏡なんです
People are mirrors,
実のところ依存は両辺です
in truth, dependency goes both ways.
シャットダウンしても付き纏う 己の弱さが不甲斐ない
Even after shutting down, it clings to me, my own weakness is so pathetic.
全部全部あんたのせいって
Saying it's all, all your fault,
反吐が出るくらいに止まんないわ
it doesn't stop, to the point of making me sick.
いっその事 切り離した方が楽なのににな
It would be so much easier to just cut you off instead.
大体アナタのコト アタシ
Generally, when it comes to you, I...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライ
really, really, really hate you!
omg 情けない 最早
Oh my god, so pathetic, at this point,
バイバイバイ バイバイしたい
I want to say bye-bye-bye, bye-bye.
脳内も 予測不能 故に
Inside my brain is unpredictable too, so,
解解 解 解解は 無い
there is no, no, no solution.
どうだい？ アタシのコト アナタ
How about it? When it comes to me, do you...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライになった？
really, really, really hate me now?
あぁ 百害あって一利ナシ
Ah, there are a hundred harms and not a single benefit,
nothing not see もしタラレバ
nothing, not see, even with "what ifs,"
並べてもニコチンだし
lining them up is just like nicotine.
i miss youって近付いた
Approaching with an "I miss you,"
結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
the ending was a clumsy mistake, a clumsy mistake.
センキュー 反面教師
Thank you, my negative role model,
後味一生消えてくんないわ
this aftertaste will never go away for the rest of my life.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
どうもー！
Thank you!
というわけでゲストは、
So, our guest is...
唯ちゃんです！
Yui-chan!
はい！改めましてネオポルテ所属の日崎唯です！
Hi! Once again, I'm Hizaki Yui from Neo-Porte!
そらさんお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-san, happy birthday!
ありがとう！来てくれて嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so glad you could come!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
1年ぶり！
It's been a year!
A year!
いや、ね。去年はね、
Yes, well, last year,
ちょっと残念ながら、メッセージだけで。
unfortunately, it was just a message.
あ、どうも...
Ah, thank you...
あの、昨年は本当に申し訳ございませんでした！
Um, I am so truly sorry about last year!
いや、あのメッセージでもね、すごくみんな「おおー！」ってなってて。
No, even with just that message, everyone went "Ooh!"
嬉しかったですよ。
I was really happy.
すごいガラガラ声でね、去年は。
My voice was so raspy last year.
参加させていただいたんですけど、
But I'm glad I could participate.
今年はリベンジができて、とっても嬉しいです！
This year, I'm so happy I got to redeem myself!
やった！リベンジだ！
Yay! Revenge!
呼んでいただいて嬉しいです、ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy you invited me, thank you!
こちらこそ！
Likewise!
今回の曲もね、私が選んだんですけども、
I chose this song for us this time,
やっぱり、唯ちゃんといえば、カッコいい声っていうのが、
and when it comes to Yui-chan, that cool voice of yours
私の中で、すごく頭の中にあって。
is really prominent in my mind.
いやぁ、嬉しい。
Wow, I'm so glad.
かっこいいよ！
You're so cool!
なので、このデュエットっていうのもあるので、
And since there's a duet version,
この曲をぜひ一緒に歌いたいと思って。
I really wanted to sing this song together.
嬉しい！ありがとうございます。
I'm so happy! Thank you so much.
どうだったかな？
How was it?
いや、あの、歌も超難しかったんですけど、
Well, the song was super difficult,
どちらかというと、ダンスが。
but if anything, the dancing was...
普段あんまりしないので、
I don't usually do much dancing.
そうだよね。
Right.
そらさんとダンスレッスンなどもね、
So I got to do dance lessons with Sora-san.
したの、したの！
We did, we did!
やらさせていただきましてですね、
I was allowed to practice with you,
本番に向けて準備してまいりました！
and we prepared for the actual performance!
でも、振りはめちゃくちゃ早くてびっくりした！
But the choreography was super fast, I was shocked!
いやいや、恐縮でございます。
No, no, you're too kind.
ちょっとね、「あー！」って言いながら練習してたよね。
We were practicing while screaming "Aaah!"
間奏で、ターンするところがあったんですけど、皆さん。
In the instrumental break, there was a part where we turn, everyone.
ターンが、本当に体幹がなさすぎて、
And I have so little core strength for turning,
「あー！」って、何回もよろけてですね、
I kept losing my balance and going "Aaah!"
大変だったんですけど。
It was really tough.
いや、でも本番は完璧だったんじゃないの？
But wasn't it absolutely perfect on stage?
あー、よかったです。
Oh, I'm glad.
素晴らしい！
Fantastic!
よろけなくて、頭の中で「よろけんじゃね、よろけんじゃね」と思いながら。
I didn't stagger! In my head I was like, "Don't wobble, don't wobble."
そうだよね。
Right.
よろけないように、って考えて。
Thinking about not wobbling.
意識しちゃうよね。
You end up conscious of it.
意識してました。そらさんが完璧なんで。
I was conscious of it. Sora-san was so perfect.
いやいや、そんなことない。
No, no, not at all.
隣に立つから、私も...
Since I was standing next to you, I felt...
まさかね、ダンスまでしてくれるとは思わなかったの。
I never expected you to do the dance with me.
だから本当に、誘ったときに「ダンスもあるんですけど」って言ったときに、
So honestly, when I invited you and said, "There's a dance, too,"
「え、ダンス？ちょっと...」ってなるかなと思ったから、
I thought you'd be like, "Oh, a dance? Uh, I don't know..."
いやいやいや、ぜひ！と思いました。
No, no, no, I was like, "I'd love to!"
本当に？！普段ね、こう、右手でどうにかしてるんで。
Really?! Since I usually, you know, just get by with my right hand...
手持ちマイクで、右手でどうにか尺稼ぎしてたんですけど、
I usually hold a mic and try to buy time with my right hand,
今日はダンスに挑戦できたのが、自分的にもすごい嬉しかったです。一緒に踊れて。
so being able to challenge myself with dancing today made me really happy. To dance together.
めちゃくちゃかっこよかった！
You looked so cool!
いえいえ、一緒に踊れて、超嬉しかったんで。
Oh, not at all. I was super happy to dance with you.
いや、私も嬉しかった！
I was happy, too!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
どうだった？
How was it?
かっこよかったでしょ？
We looked cool, right?
頑張ったぞ！
We did our best!
頑張ったよ！
We really did!
はい。という感じで、このあともね、またライブがあるということなので、
Yes! And so, since there's more live performance to come,
このあともぜひ頑張ってください！
please do your best for the rest of it!
頑張る！
I will!
応援してます！
I'm rooting for you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、ということで、ネオポルテの日月ゆいでした！ありがとうございました！
Okay, that was Hizuki Yui from Neo-Porte! Thank you very much!
日月ゆいでした！
This was Hizuki Yui!
頑張ってね！ありがとうね！
Good luck! - Thank you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
ておー！ておー！あははは。
Teo! - Teo! Haha!
ということで、ひづきちゃんが、来てくれました。
And so, Hizuki-chan came to visit.
ひづきちゃんって言った？ちょっと待って。
Did I say "Hizuki-chan"? Wait a minute.
ゆいちゃんが来てくれました！嬉しいね！
Yui-chan came to visit! I'm so happy!
というわけで、あっという間なんだけど、私、口癖「というわけで」なんだな。今気づいちゃった。
And so, it's gone by in a flash... I guess my catchphrase is "and so." I just realized that.
ここからライブ後半戦です！
From here, it's the second half of the live show!
それでは、5曲目、聞いてください。
So now, please listen to the 5th song.
「モニタリング」。
"Monitoring."
ねえ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙流してるの知ってるよ
Hey, I know... I know you're crying all by yourself.
びくんびくん震えてさ 声もだるだるなんだわ 正直に
You're shaking and trembling, and your voice sounds so exhausted, honestly.
言っちゃえばバレてるんだし 言っちゃえば聞いてんの？
If we're being honest, it's obvious. If we're being honest, are you listening?
ふつうふつう平気だよ みんな分かってないだけ むふふ
"I'm totally fine," you say, but they just don't get it. Hehe.
もしもし？ねえ、大丈夫？うん、心配だから、今からそっち行くね。
Hello? Hey, are you okay? Yeah, I'm worried, so I'm coming over to your place now.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙流してるの知ってるよ
Hey, I know... I know you're crying all by yourself.
ぐすぐす凹んでさ ヨワネハイトカデイインジャナイ？
Sobbing and feeling down... Isn't it okay to vent your weaknesses?
朝が来るまで一緒 交信もっと泣いたって 何度も何度も受け止めてあげる
Together until morning, connecting even more. No matter how much you cry, I'll embrace you over and over.
もう我慢しないでいっぱい吐いてね むー
Don't hold it back anymore, just let it all out. Mmm...
おねがい君が欲しいの 慰めさせてベストフレンド
Please, I want you. Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の変化球で泣いてくれるかい？
With the talent of love, will you cry for me?
君のツラい、抱きしめたい ねえ、いいでしょ？
I want to hold your pain tight, hey, is that okay?
分け合って乗り越えたいんだんだんだってば
I want us to share it and overcome it, I'm telling you!
むー おねがい君が欲しいの
Mmm... Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばしてほらステップ ジャンプ、最高で分けてくれるかい？
Laugh it off and take a step, jump! Will you share your best with me?
君に重い、ツラい、重い ねえ、いいでしょ？
Your heavy, painful, heavy feelings... Hey, is that okay?
寄り添って救いたいんだんだんだってば
I want to stay close and save you, I'm telling you!
みたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいの君の涙
I want to see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see your tears.
みたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたいみたい
I want to see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see...
ねえ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人悔しがってるの知ってるよ
Hey, I know... I know you're feeling frustrated all by yourself.
ぐすぐす終わるまで君を消して諦めない
Until you stop sobbing, I will never give up on you.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ 君はできる子知ってるよ
Hey, I know... I know you can do it.
ツラいときは弱い暗いでちょうどいい あたし君の味方だよ
When times are tough, being weak and gloomy is just right. I'm on your side.
むー おねがい君が欲しいの 名前を呼んでよ
Mmm... Please, I want you. Call my name.
いつだって愛に参上 君は一人か？
I'll always fly to your side with love. Are you alone?
それは違う、一人じゃない もういいでしょ？
That's not true, you're not alone. Isn't that enough?
ソロプレイはお終いなんだんだんだってば
Solo play is over, I'm telling you!
君がどんなときも
No matter when or what you're going through,
あたしそばにいるわ
I will be right by your side.
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'll always be watching over you. Yes, you don't have to be afraid.
おーおおー
Oh, oh, oh...
むー おねがい君が欲しいの 慰めさせてベストフレンド
Mmm... Please, I want you. Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の変化球で泣いてくれるかい？
With the talent of love, will you cry for me?
君のツラい、抱きしめたい ねえ、いいでしょ？
I want to hold your pain tight, hey, is that okay?
分け合って乗り越えたいんだんだんだってば
I want us to share it and overcome it, I'm telling you!
むー おねがい君が欲しいの
Mmm... Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばしてほらステップ ジャンプ、最高で分けてくれるかい？
Laugh it off and take a step, jump! Will you share your best with me?
君に重い、ツラい、重い、届きたい
My heavy, painful, heavy feelings for you, I want to reach you.
寄り添って救いたいんだんだんだってば
I want to stay close and save you, I'm telling you!
ねえ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙流してるの知ってるよ
Hey, I know... I know you're crying all by yourself.
ぐすぐす凹んでさ ヨワネハイトカデイインジャナイ？
Sobbing and feeling down... Isn't it okay to vent your weaknesses?
ずっと一緒交信もっと泣いたって 何度も何度も受け止めてあげる
Forever together, connecting even more. No matter how much you cry, I'll embrace you over and over.
もう我慢しないで出しててててってば
Don't hold it back anymore, just let it all out, I'm telling you!
はーい！ということで、新衣装でーす！
Tada! And so, here is my new outfit!
みんな、可愛い？
Everyone, is it cute?
気になるとは思うけど、紹介はあとで。
I know you're curious, but the details will come later.
先にゲストの方と歌うよ！
First, I'm going to sing with my next guest!
どうぞ！
Here they come!
僕らよ 始まれ
Let us begin,
青く 青く 果てまで
blue and blue, to the very end.
真夜中の境目を分けたバースデイ
A birthday that parted the boundary of midnight,
どこにいたって足りない
no matter where I am, it's not enough.
命は一つじゃ足りない
One life is not enough.
まだ剥がせないこの脳内に
Still unable to peel it away inside my brain,
不思議な夢を見る
I dream a mysterious dream.
どこまでもいけると
That I can go anywhere,
どうしてか信じたくなった
for some reason, I wanted to believe.
跳ねる鼓動 誰を呼ぶの ベルの音
A bouncing heartbeat, who does it call? The sound of the bell.
どうして待って 同調（シンクロ）する瞬間（とき）が 自分の主導（イニシアチブ）
Why wait? The moment we synchronize is under my initiative.
あっという間に終わる祭りはない
There's no festival that ends in the blink of an eye.
おそれさえも笑い合おう
Let's laugh away even our fears,
共にいよう
let's be together.
痛って 不完全体
Even if it hurts, this incomplete body
故に思いは強くなってきた
makes our feelings grow even stronger.
深くの夜を越え
Crossing the deep night,
空白に願い唱え
chanting a wish into the blank space.
諦め崩された世界を
The world ruined by giving up,
君と二人 泥に転がり回る
tumbling in the mud with you.
混ざり合い
Blending together,
そして生まれ変わるような
as if being reborn.
きっと僕らだけが保存
Surely only we
なせるパレード
can make this parade.
絶対証明したい 進化したい 才能超えて 瞬間（とき）を越えたい
I want absolute proof, I want to evolve, surpassing talent, surpassing time.
シースー そうしたい となりにいたい
Seesaw, I want to do that, I want to be by your side.
過酷な現実は僕を引き留めたがり
Harsh reality tries to hold me back,
覚悟の境界線 右か左か
the boundary line of resolve, left or right?
今はそこに君がいる保存
Now you are there,
未知なるバージョン 確定だよ
the unknown version is confirmed!
まだ見ぬ世界へ
To a world yet unseen,
行こうか
shall we go?
僕らよ 始まれ
Let us begin,
青く 青く 果てまで
blue and blue, to the very end.
痛って 不完全体
Even if it hurts, this incomplete body
故に思いは強くなってきた
makes our feelings grow even stronger.
深くの夜を越え
Crossing the deep night,
空白に願い唱え
chanting a wish into the blank space.
諦め崩された世界を
The world ruined by giving up,
君と二人 泥に転がり回る
tumbling in the mud with you.
混ざり合い
Blending together,
そして生まれ変わるような保存
as if being reborn.
きっと僕らこそが
Surely only we
なせるパレード
can make this parade.
不完全体 パレード
Incomplete parade.
はい、というわけで！
All right, and with that!
ゲストの前にちょっとね、今ね...
Before the next guest, just now...
東北の方で地震があったみたいですが大丈夫でしょうか？
it seems there was an earthquake in Tohoku. Is everyone okay?
東北の方、身の回りの安全を優先でお願いします。
To those in Tohoku, please prioritize your safety.
気をつけるんだよ！気をつけてください！
Please be careful! Please stay safe!
そして、次のゲストはリオナちゃんです！
And our next guest is Riona-chan!
はい！プロプロのリーダー、響咲リオナです！プロプロ〜
Yes! The leader of Puropro, Riona Hibiki! Puropro!
そして、そら先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Also, Sora-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！嬉しい！保存
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
今日はね、あの、最近めちゃくちゃ仲良いっていうのと、やっぱり...
Today, well, since we've been getting super close lately...
お歌とダンスと言えば、なんというか、今はリオナちゃんってイメージがあって
and when I think of singing and dancing, I immediately picture Riona-chan.
嬉しい！
I'm so glad!
一緒にあの、歌いたいと思って、呼んじゃいました！
So I wanted us to sing together, and invited her!
本当に嬉しかったです、呼んでもらえた時！
I was really happy when you invited me!
それで、それで！そら先輩！保存
And, and! Sora-senpai!
何ですか？新衣装じゃないですか！めちゃくちゃ可愛い！
What is it? Isn't that your new outfit?! It's so cute!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
どんな衣装なんですか？
What kind of outfit is it?
こちらはですね、去年出したアルバムの「Parade」っていう...
This is actually the outfit from my album 'Parade'...
のジャケットで、あの、使った衣装なんですけど。もう実際にライブでも着たいと思って、仕立てて...
...that was used for the jacket cover. I really wanted to wear it for a live performance, so I had it made...
いただきました！
We received it!
あらもうそらともさんも、そらともさんも「ちゅー」って感じじゃないですか？
My, aren't the Soratomos also feeling like "chu"?
「ちゅー」って感じになっちゃうかもしれない！
They might end up feeling like "chu"!
じゃあ、あの、しーちゃんを見習って、りおなが来た意味をね、今から私もやっていこうと思うんですけど。
So, following Shi-chan's lead, I'll show the meaning of Riona's arrival from now on.
何ですか？
What is it?
まあ、みんなもね、写真がいっぱい撮りたいと思うんですよ。
Well, I'm sure everyone wants to take lots of photos.
そうですね。
That's true.
りおな直伝のセクシーポーズ写真集、どうですか？
How about a sexy pose photoshoot taught directly by Riona?
やるやる！
I'll do it, I'll do it!
スクショ大会！
A screenshot contest!
こんな大会？
A contest like this?
大会です、もうこれは！
It's definitely a contest!
大会だった...
It was a contest...
あの、セクシーなポーズを直伝、直伝してくれるので、
Um, she'll teach us sexy poses directly, so...
はい。
Yes.
それをね、そらともさんに写真撮ってもらうという回でも。私はもう画面外で...
This will be a time for Soratomos to take photos. I'll just be off-screen...
え、何で？
Eh, why?
後で一緒に撮るのね。
We'll take them together later.
あ、オッケーです。
Ah, okay.
じゃあ、まず、
Then, first...
えー、やっぱ、りおなといえば、あ、これ。りおなといえば、もうこれですから。
Well, when you think of Riona, it has to be this.
こうやって切るのかな、私。
Am I supposed to pose like this?
これ、ちょっと。ちょっと足をこう...
This, wait. Move your leg like this...
私できない、ちょっと。
I can't do it, wait.
色々アウト、色々アウト！こういうのはどうですか？こういうの。
That's a bit too suggestive! How about this instead?
あ、こういうのね。
Ah, like this.
あ、もうりおなはね、行きますから、どっか。
Well, Riona will step away for a bit.
あ、いいですね、いいですね！
Ah, nice, nice!
あ、いい！ちょっと右手を前に出しちゃったりして。
Oh, nice! Try putting your right hand forward.
あー、いいですね、いいですね！
Ah, yes, nice, nice!
あ、ちょっと、あー、いい！うまい！
Ah, wait, oh, nice! You're good!
あれ？
Huh?
そら先輩、セクシーの才能がかなりあるんじゃないですか？
Sora-senpai, don't you have a real talent for being sexy?
おおー、素晴らしい！
Ooh, wonderful!
え、あとはどうしようかな。
Um, what should we do next?
ちょっと、あ、いや、いいの？それで。
Wait, ah, is that really okay?
そういうことじゃないの、セクシーって。
That's not what sexy is!
まあちょっと教える必要なかったですよ、これ。
Well, I didn't even need to teach you this.
あ、うわ、ちょっと、あ、ちょっと！
Ah, wow, wait, ah, wait!
後ろからのアングルめっちゃいいな。
The angle from behind is really good.
ちょっと！楽しまないでよ！
Wait! Don't enjoy this so much!
ごめん、ごめん。
Sorry, sorry.
あの、なんかね、こういうのとかね。
Well, like, something like this.
いや、ほう、みたいな。後ろからの、イェーイ！
Like, "whoa". From behind, yay!
あ、いいですね、いいですね！可愛い！
Ah, nice, nice! So cute!
色とりどりでめっちゃ綺麗ですね。
It's so colorful and beautiful.
そらのこのグラデーションが入ってて可愛いんだよ。
Sora's gradient makes it so cute.
メッチャ可愛い！
Super cute!
え、じゃあ一緒に写ってくれますか？
Then, will you pose with me?
もちろんだよ。
Of course.
そらりおポーズ考えようって言ってたのに、全然考えられなかった。
We said we'd think of a Sora-Lio pose, but we didn't think of one at all.
なんかね、クマと、なんか、りおなっぽいポーズがあって、りおなの公式ポーズがこれなんですけど、
Well, there's a Riona-like pose... Riona's official pose is this, but...
私はこうなんだよね。
And mine is like this.
そう、だからそしたらなんか、ほぼ似てるみたいな。
Right, so if we do that, they're almost identical.
ほぼ一緒だね。
Almost the same.
そしたら、クマと手をやる、こう、これがいいんじゃないかなって思ってるんですけど、みなさんどうですか？
So, doing this with the bear and hand... I think this would be good, what does everyone think?
どうですか？
What do you think?
そらりおポーズ。
The Sora-Lio pose.
クマとのばし。
Bear and stretch.
あん肝とのばし。
Ankimo and stretch.
え、あとあれですよ。最近、私のこと飲んでるって本当ですか？
Also, is it true you've been drinking me lately?
そう！りおな茶を！
Yes! Lio-tea!
貧血の、りおな茶を！
The anemic-care Lio-tea!
凄く助かって、今。
It really helps me now.
本当ですか？じゃあもういつでも呼び出してください。りおな吸われに行くんで。
Really? Then, call me anytime. I'll come be absorbed.
あ、ありがとうございます。そら先輩どうぞ、って。
Ah, thank you. "Here you go, Sora-senpai!"
うわあ！
Whoa!
助かる。私が助かる。いつでもね、あの、供給しますんで。
That helps. It helps me. I'll supply it anytime.
ありがとうございます。いつでも呼んでくださいね。
Thank you. Please call me anytime.
はーい！
Okay!
あれ？りおな、吸い込まれてる！そら先輩助けて！
Huh? Riona is being sucked in! Sora-senpai, help!
そら先輩！そら先輩！
Sora-senpai! Sora-senpai!
ああー！
Aah!
ほら！みんな、みんなそれをやっていくんだ！みんなそれをやっていくんだ！
Look! Everyone, everyone is going to do that! Everyone is going to do that!
さあ、でもね、りおなちゃんとはね、本当に仲が良くて。いつもね、よく会うんですけど。
Well, Riona-chan and I are really close. We always meet up often.
いつもと変わらない、可愛い感じでしたね。私が消えましたね、ごめんなさい。
She had her usual cute vibe. Oh, I disappeared, sorry.
お水を飲みに行ってました。はい。
I went to drink some water. Yes.
というわけで、続いてのゲストは、もう誰だかわかるよね？
So, you already know who the next guest is, right?
この人です！
It's this person!
[GUEST：風真いろは]
[Guest: Kazama Iroha]
はーい！
Hello!
真夜中に告ぐ 音の警告
A sound gives its warning in the middle of the night
協和音に酔う 午前零時
I'm intoxicated by the consonance at midnight
あなたが触れる 光増す熱
With your touch, a light, an increasing fever
指先にとどまる
You have me dancing on your fingertip
感覚 即 体感
I have an intuition, suddenly, a sensation
寝静まる夜 二人だけの密
Our secret nectar in the sleeping night
体感 即 快感
I have a sensation, suddenly, a pleasant feeling
重なる波形に魅了されていく
I'm fascinated by the overlapping waveforms
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even through a screen, love me properly
バーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Even if I'm virtual, don't cast me aside
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
Gazing at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と音とヒビカセ
Let our overlapped breaths and sounds resonate
真夜中に問う 冷え切った熱
Questioning the chilled fever in the dead of night
待ち続けてる 午前零時
I keep on waiting for midnight
鏡写しに 飽和していく
Saturating in a mirror image
知らない音が伝う
An unfamiliar sound is transmitted
感覚即体感 寝静まる夜と
Sensation to immediate experience, in the quiet night
息遣い揃う
our breaths fall into unison.
体感即快感
Experience to immediate pleasure
錆びたロジック 「今一度」を焦がれる
The rusted logic yearns for "just once more."
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't forget my voice
次元も越えて 飛ばすシグナル
A signal sent flying across dimensions
バーチャルだなんて 言わないで
Don't say things like "it's just virtual"
あなたの音に まだ愛されていたい
I still want to be loved by your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
言の葉と 初の音が交わる
Words and the first sound intertwine
この息と音とヒビカセ
With this breath and sound, let it resonate
あぁ あなたの生んだ音に
Ah, to the sound you created
あぁ ただ恋をしていたの
Ah, I was simply in love
悲しみ 怒り 感情 すべて打ち鳴らす
Sadness, anger, feelings, ringing out all of them
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly crying out, linking voices together
余熱交ぜる 愛絶え艶めく
Mixing lingering heat, love fading and blooming
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly crying out, linking voices together
余熱交ぜる 愛絶え艶めく
Mixing lingering heat, love fading and blooming
魅了されていく
Becoming captivated
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even through a screen, love me properly
バーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Even if I'm virtual, don't cast me aside
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
Gazing at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と音をヒビカセ
Let our overlapped breaths and sounds resonate
あぁ あぁ あぁ あぁ
Ah, ah, ah, ah
あなたの初の音 この声聴かせ
Let me hear your first sound, and this voice
音とヒビカセ
Let it resonate with the sound
はい！というわけで最後のゲストは、いろはちゃんでーす！
Yes! And so, our final guest is Iroha-chan!
いえーい！
Yay!
ホロックスの、強い、
HoloX's strong,
イケmen、早い、カッコいい...
cool, fast, awesome...
うーん、なんかすごい、風真いろはでーす！いえーい！
Hmm, somehow super amazing, Kazama Iroha! Yay!
おかしいな...
That's strange...
そら先輩、
Sora-senpai,
お誕生日おめでとうございます！
happy birthday!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
おかしいな...
That's strange...
何がおかしいんだい？
What's strange?
リハーサル日まではあんなにメロついてくれてたのに...
Until the rehearsal day, you were so lovey-dovey with me...
すごいじゃん。今日のために...
That's great. Does that mean...
整えてくれたってこと？
you prepared yourself just for today?
今日のために、
For today,
ちょっと整えさせていただきました。
I tidied myself up a bit.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
コメント欄のみんなもあんなにメロついてくれてたのに、
Everyone in the comments was so lovey-dovey too,
今日は全然メロついてない！
but today they aren't at all!
いやいやいや、そんなことなかったよ！カッコいい二人とも！って書いてあったよ。
No, no, no, that's not true! They wrote "Both of you are so cool!"
え、ホントですか？
Really?
ホントに？ちょっともう一回見たいから「カッコいい」って書いてもらっていいですか？
Really? I want to see it again, so could you write "cool"?
カッコいいって、みんなカッコいいって書いて！
Write "cool", everyone write "cool"!
可愛い、可愛い、可愛い...可愛いのは当たり前じゃん！
Cute, cute, cute... Well, being cute is a given!
あ、そう、そっか。
Ah, right, that's true.
ござるちゃんはいつでも可愛い。
Gozaru-chan is always cute.
ほら、カッコいい、カッコいいって！
Look, they're writing "cool, cool"!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
お前たちのカッコいいが義務だとしても風真いろはは嬉しいぞ！
Even if your "cool" is mandatory, Kazama Iroha is still happy!
え、あの、一人でも記念配信の時歌ってたけど...
Uh, well, you sang it during your solo anniversary stream too...
それすごく似合ってたから、一緒に歌いたいなと思って呼んじゃいました！
It suited you so well, so I wanted to sing it together and invited you!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
嬉しくて死んでしまう！
I'm so happy I could die!
生きて！生きて！
Live! Live!
生きてますよ、生きてます。
I'm alive, I'm alive.
あ、良かった良かった。
Ah, good, good.
いや、でも元々、やっぱりそら先輩と言えばボカロ曲めっちゃ似合うなって思ってたんで、
No, but originally, I always thought Vocaloid songs suit Sora-senpai so well.
いつかやってくんないかなって、
I always hoped you'd do it someday...
オタクとして思ってたんですけど、
as an otaku.
まさか自分がゲストとして...
But to think I'd be here as a guest...
呼んでもらえるなんて！
and actually get invited!
こんな有り難いことがあっていいのか！
Can such a wonderful thing really happen?!
でも、一緒に二人で歌ったことがなかったから、歌ってみたくて。
But we've never sung together as a duo, so I really wanted to try singing with you.
確かに！「ほしまち」… Hoshimaticだとね、結構ね…
True! With Hoshimatic, we often...
そうそう。ついやってること多いんですけどね。
Right, right. We often end up doing things together.
フェスとかでも歌ったけど、3人とかだったから。
We've sung at festivals, but that was with three of us.
そう、だからデュエットってやったことがなくて。
Yeah, so we've never actually done a duet.
確かに。
That's true.
ねー。
Right?
ありがたいお話でございました、本当に。
It was a truly wonderful opportunity.
本当にこちらこそ！
No, thank you!
貴重な体験を！ / いやいや、こちらこそありがとうございます、本当に。
For such a precious experience! / No, no, thank you so much, really!
はーい、はーい。
Yes, yes.
いや、それにしても、今日これ、新衣装なんですよね！
But anyway, you're wearing your new outfit today, right?
そうなんですよ、新衣装なんですよ。
That's right, it's my new outfit!
新衣装なんですよね、どう？
It's your new outfit! How is it?
おー、おー。
Ooh, ooh!
いや、ちょっとね、さっきリョーナさんがね、なんか結構きわどいこと言っていたんですけど、
Well, Ryona-san was saying some pretty risqué things earlier...
やはりね、ちょっとこっちのクイクイタイプオタクとして一個いいでしょうか？
But as a "kui-kui" type of otaku, can I say one thing?
何でしょう？
What is it?
やはり、オタクというものはですね、やっぱあの、一肌脱いだ姿が気になるっていうものでございまして。
After all, otakus can't help but be curious about what lies beneath!
あの、この隠されている純白が、あの、この姿で見れるのかっていうのが凄く気になっておりまして。ええ、本当に。
I'm really curious if we'll get to see the pure white hidden underneath this look. Yes, really.
だって、この下のなんかも、清楚感あふれるこれ、絶対みんな気になってるでしょ？
I mean, everyone must be curious about this pure-looking thing underneath, right?
いや、オタクとしてもう気になりますよ、こんなの！
As an otaku, I'm definitely curious about this!
そうですよね。
Right.
でも、この配信の中では、ちょっとまだ見せられないかなー。
But I can't show it just yet during this stream.
え？え？も、もしかして、そ、それは、脱げるということでござるか？
Huh? Huh? Wait, does that mean... you CAN take it off?
この配信の中では見せることはないんだけど…
I won't be showing it in this stream, but...
あいさら！メン限に入れ！メン限だったら見れるかもしれないぞ！
Guys, join the members-only stream! We might see it there!
はい、いや、楽しみにしておりますので。
Yes! Well, I'll be looking forward to it.
こちらこそ！
Me too!
メン限に入れ？ / 入れ？
Join the members-only stream? / Join?
メン限に入れ？強制的！
Join the members-only stream? Forcefully!
だって、これ、あの、脱いだ姿が見れるんですよね？
I mean, we get to see the look with it off, right?
この後も楽しみにしていますよ！
I'll be looking forward to what comes next!
というわけで、そら先輩、まだこの後も全然続くと思うんですけど、
So, Sora-senpai, I know there's still a lot more to come, but...
頑張ってください！
Please do your best!
頑張るよ！
I'll do my best!
プロとしてお待ちしておりますので。
I'll be waiting for you as a pro.
そうね、また後でね。
Right, see you later.
プロとして。 / プロとして。
As a pro. / As a pro.
あ、やばい、プロの世界に引き込まれてしまう。あー！
Oh no, I'm being drawn into the world of pros. Ah!
プロの世界に引き込まれ…でもござるわね、上品だから。あの、お尻叩かないで！
Drawn into the world of pros... but wait, because I'm elegant... please don't spank me!
ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you.
未来で待ってる。
I'll wait for you in the future.
未来で待っててくれ。 / 指なんだ。
Please wait for me in the future. / Oh, it's a finger!
ふふふ、さあ何、
Fufu, now...
何よね、あの、また後でって、どういうことなんでしょうかね。
What did she mean by "see you later" anyway?
はい、プロとして、何のプロなんでしょうか。
Yes, "as a pro"... what kind of pro is she?
気になる方、あ、ライブに、来てもらって。
For those who are curious, please come to the live show...
嬉しいなと思います。
I'd be very happy.
さて、ちょっとお待ちくださいね。
Now, please wait a moment.
いよいよ終盤戦です。
We're finally entering the final part.
あ、お水おいしい！
Ah, the water is delicious!
ふふふ、はーい。
Hehehe, alright.
いよいよ終盤戦なんですけど、
We're finally entering the final part...
最後まで盛り上がっていってください！
But please keep the hype up until the very end!
もしかしたら、あの子が来ちゃうかもね。
Who knows, maybe THAT girl will show up.
ふふふ、聴いてください。プレイ。
Hehe. Please listen to "Play".
いいか ちょけろ ちょけろ
Listen, stop messing around, stop messing around
さぁ図に乗って いい加減にしろ
Now stop getting cocky, that's enough
やめらんないねぇ どうしようもねぇ
I can't stop, it's helpless
言い訳なら後で 考えてくれてやる
I'll let you think of an excuse later
王道とか下らねぇな 毎回
The classic path is so boring every time
自意識過剰なやつ徘徊
Self-conscious folks wandering around
みんなが右往左往する間に こちとら地に足つけてきたぜ ハイハイ
While everyone runs around in confusion, I've got my feet on the ground, yeah yeah
どうした？ みんな浮かない顔して
What's wrong? Why does everyone look so down?
絵空事 大歓迎よ
Pipe dreams are most welcome
現実味ねぇよ
There's no reality to it
早く楽になりたい？
Do you want to be put out of your misery quickly?
いつでもいいよ おねんねさせたれ
Anytime is fine, let's put them to sleep
nothing to do with you
ちょけろ ちょけろ
Stop messing around, stop messing around
さぁ図に乗って いい加減にしろ
Now stop getting cocky, that's enough
やめらんないねぇ はぜろ はぜろ
I can't stop, burst, burst
おおおおお 責任だってとるよ墓場までは
Oh, oh, oh, I'll take responsibility, all the way to the grave
堂々とだけさせてくれよ こちとらマイペースなトラブルメーカー
Just let me do my thing, I'm a trouble maker moving at my own pace
とりあえず取扱説明書 隅から隅まで読んでおきな
For now, read the instruction manual from cover to cover
ヒヤッとしたって なぜか
Even if you get cold feet, for some reason...
ニヤッとしちゃうのおかしいな
You end up smirking, isn't that strange?
とめろ とめろ とめろ とめろ！
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it!
絵空事 大歓迎よ
Pipe dreams are most welcome
現実味ねぇよ
There's no reality to it
早く楽になりたい？
Do you want to be put out of your misery quickly?
いつでもいいよ おねんねさせたれ
Anytime is fine, let's put them to sleep
nothing to do with you
押せよ そのリセットボタン
Go ahead and push that reset button
消せよ お前のその価値観
Erase those values of yours
どうせ何度でも元に戻せるなら
Since you can reset it as many times as you want anyway
指くわえて見てるだけじゃ つまらない やいやい
It's no fun just standing by watching idly, yeah yeah
思いっきり前ノリ気味
Leaning forward with all my might
止まる気ないアクセルベタ踏み
Floor the accelerator with no intention of stopping
ねぇ are you kidding?
Hey, are you kidding?
はい、ちょ、まって
Yes, wait, hold on
ここでストップ
Stop right here
return to the start
ぜってーやべーよ！
This is definitely crazy!
話がちげーぞ！
That's not what we agreed on!
早く楽になりたい？
Do you want to be put out of your misery quickly?
いつでもいいよ おねんねさせたれ
Anytime is fine, let's put them to sleep
nothing to do with you
Nothing can get over it!
押せよ そのリセットボタン
Press that reset button.
消せよ マイナスのアンサー
Erase the negative answer.
本当はもう二度と戻ってこれないから
Because the truth is, we can never return again.
調子にのせてよ のせてみせるのが
So let me get carried away, showing I can do it,
楽でいいのかもしれないな
as that might just be the easy way out.
はい！ありがとうございました！
Yes! Thank you very much!
この曲、「プレイ」を歌わせていただきました！
I performed the song "Play"!
そして、この曲では、なんとサングラスをかけたあんきもがやってきました！
And for this song, Ankimo actually showed up wearing sunglasses!
どうしてサングラス？
Why the sunglasses?
わあ、取れた！
Wow, they came off!
遊ぶんじゃないの、もう！
Hey, stop playing around!
というわけで、久々にあんきもと一緒に何か踊った気がするんだけど、どう？
So, I feel like it's been a while since I danced with Ankimo. What did you think?
５人目のゲスト、あんきもです！
Our fifth guest is Ankimo!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ある意味シークレットだった、めっちゃ踊るやん！
He was a secret guest in a way. Look at him dance!
そしてね、そんな感じで、
So, with that being said,
まだね、最後にちょっとお披露目もあるんだけど、
we still have a little reveal at the end,
ここでね、
but before that,
まずは恒例のお知らせがたくさんあるので、
we have many of our usual announcements,
ここからはあんきもと一緒に告知していくね！
so I'll share them together with Ankimo from here on!
聞いてください！まずはこちら！
Listen up! First is this!
ときのそら誕生日記念2020グッズです！
Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration 2020 Goods!
順番に紹介していくよ！
I'll introduce them one by one!
まずは、こちら！
First up is this!
Dream!そらとも法被！イラストは、おるだん先生です！
The "Dream! Soratomo Happi"! The illustration is by Orudan-sensei!
テーマは、「ライブをしてる私」ということで、なんとあんきももいっぱいいるんだよ！
The theme is "Me performing live," and it actually features lots of Ankimo too!
ね！今までも、オリジナル法被自体はイベントとかで出たことはあるんですけど、
Right? We've released custom happi coats at events before,
自分でオリジナルで作るのは初めてだったので、
but this is the first time I've custom-made one myself,
ぜひライブで着てきてほしいなと思って作りました！
so I made it hoping you'll wear it to my concerts!
ぜひぜひみんな楽しんでくださいね！
I hope everyone enjoys it!
ライブに来てください！
Please come to the concert!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
「お部屋でのんびり」ワイドラバーマット！
The "Relaxing in My Room" Wide Rubber Mat!
イェーイ！イラストは、しわすたかし先生です！
Yay! The illustration is by Shiwasu Takashi-sensei!
テーマは、「部屋でファンレターを読んでいる私」で、こちらね、ホロカの
The theme is "Me reading fan letters in my room." This one is actually
やつにね、丁度いいサイズになってるので、
the perfect size for Holoca,
ホロカを遊ぶ方、ぜひぜひ一緒にね、持って行って
so if you play Holoca, please bring it along
遊んでもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
and play with it! I'd be so happy!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
そらとおそろいスマホリング！
The "Matching Smartphone Ring with Sora"!
ということでね、前回販売したDJそらパーカーとデザインが
The design matches the DJ Sora Hoodie
一緒なので、それと一緒に合わせてスマホも
we sold last time, so you can pair it
私とおそろっちみたいにしませんか？
to have your phone match mine!
という感じです！
That's the idea!
そして、続いては、こちら！
And next is this!
そらザウルスなりきりそらちゃんぬいぐるみ！
The "Sora-saurus Kigurumi Sora-chan Plushie"!
みんな、みんながあまりにもさ、「そらザウルス、そらザウルス」って言うからさ、
Because everyone kept calling me "Sora-saurus" so much...
でも「そらザウルス」自体を言うのはちょっと恥ずかしかったから、
But calling myself "Sora-saurus" was a bit embarrassing,
そらちゃんぬいぐるみ、私が着ていることにする「なりきりぬいぐるみ」にしました！
so I made this plushie where it looks like I'm wearing the kigurumi!
しかもね、これ、取る、フードが取れると、
And what's cool is, if you take off the hood,
もうピンクの衣装を着てる私みたいになるので、
it looks just like me in my pink outfit!
ぜひぜひフードを取り外して、可愛く持ち歩いてくれてもいいんじゃないかなと思います！
So I think it'd be great to take off the hood and carry it around with you!
そして、最後はこちら！
And finally, this one!
ASMRボイス、ボイタイトル「届いてるよ、きみの応援」ということで、
An ASMR Voice pack titled "I Hear Your Support"!
部屋でファンレターを読んでいるシチュエーションになっておりますので、
It features a scenario where I'm reading fan letters in my room,
ぜひぜひ皆さん、どんな風にファンレター読んでるのかなと想像しながら聞いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
so I hope you enjoy listening to it while imagining how I read your letters!
そして、フルセット購入特典は、こちら！
And here is the Full Set Purchase Bonus!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードと、
A postcard with a handwritten signature & foil-stamped message,
特典ボイス、ボイタイトルは「誕生日を迎えて」になります！
and a bonus voice track titled "Welcoming My Birthday"!
というわけでですね、皆さん急がなくて大丈夫です！
So everyone, there's no need to rush!
数量限定ではございませんので、皆さん全員分の
These are not limited in quantity, so I will write
サインを書かせていただきます！
signatures for absolutely everyone!
いくらでも書きますので、ぜひぜひ皆さん、
I'll write as many as it takes, so please,
たくさんの人にグッズを買ってもらえたら、私はとても
if many people get my merchandise, I will be
そらち大喜び！なので、よろしくお願いいたします！
super-duper happy! So please check it out!
以上、ときのそら誕生日記念2020グッズでした！みんなよろしくね！
And that's all for the Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration 2020 Goods! Thank you, everyone!
続いてのお知らせは、こちら！
Next up is this announcement!
11月ワンマンライブの「ときのそら生誕記念先行チケット販売開始」ということで、
Pre-sales for tickets to my November solo live concert "Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration" have begun!
ぴあアリーナのですね、先行チケットが本日から始まっております！
Pre-sales for the Pia Arena MM concert start today!
ぴあアリーナ、ファンクラブに入ってる人しかできないんじゃないかって言ってた人、
For those who thought only fan club members could apply,
本日から一般の皆さんも販売が開始されておりますので、
general ticket sales have actually started today,
ぜひぜひ、もう12時から開始されております！
and they've been open since 12:00 PM!
応募していただけたら嬉しいです！みんなでぴあアリーナでライブ楽しもう！
I'd be so happy if you applied! Let's all have fun at Pia Arena!
さらに！こちら！
Furthermore, look at this!
その現地チケットの特典でもらえる、ホロカのお披露目！これもお披露目でございました！
A reveal of the Holoca card you get as a venue ticket bonus! Yes, this is also a reveal!
ライブの来場者特典として、限定ホロカが1枚配られます！
As an attendee bonus, you'll receive one limited Holoca card!
全2種類のうち1枚をランダムでお渡しするのですが、そちらの1枚を公開です！
You'll randomly get one of the two types, and here's a look at one of them!
私が描き下ろしたということで、もう一個の方は
I draw this illustration myself! As for the other design...
まだ、なので...
It's not ready yet, so...
ぜひこちらのほうで ちょっと...
So please, with this...
満足していただけないでしょうか？
...won't you be satisfied?
そして 9周年ライブを記念して こちら！
And to commemorate the 9th anniversary live, here's this!
スペシャルテレビCM放送決定！ということで
A special TV CM broadcast has been decided!
本日22時半から23時の間で TOKYO MXさんの方で...
It will air tonight between 22:30 and 23:00 on TOKYO MX!
流れます 一度だけなので...
It will only air once...
ぜひ見てくれると嬉しいなと思います！よろしくお願いします！
...so I'd be really happy if you watched it! Thank you!
そしてそして 最後のお知らせがこちら！
And now, the final announcement is this!
お待たせしました！こちらです！新曲『決意のソラへ』です！
Sorry to keep you waiting! Here it is! My new song, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
私的にはエモい感じの曲というか 泣き曲かなって思ったんだけど...
Personally, I felt it was a very emotional tearjerker song...
ディレクターさん的には『泣き曲とかエモとかそういうんじゃなく 熱い曲！』みたいな...
But the director said, "It's not a tearjerker, it's a passionate song!"
『オープニングにふさわしいぐらいの熱い曲を作ったつもり』と言っていたので
They said they made it passionate enough to be an anime opening theme.
このあとね MVプレミア公開も予定されているので
The MV will premiere right after this,
各種音楽サイトでも配信されています ぜひたくさん聴いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
and it's out on streaming platforms. I'd love it if you listened to it a lot!
はい というわけで とっても楽しかったんですけど いかがだったでしょうか
Yes, so it was really fun. How did you like it?
告知がね 洪水のようになってやってきたと思うので あとでみんな確認してもらえると嬉しいなと思います
I threw a flood of announcements at you, so please check them out later!
メインは21時半からアフターライブがあるんですけど
After this, we have the After Live starting at 21:30,
スペシャルあんきもが なんと見れるかもしれないんだって スペシャルだよ スペシャル！
and you might get to see a special Ankimou! It's special!
このサングラスあんきももスペシャルではあるんだけど さらにスペシャルなあんきもが...
This sunglasses version is special, but an even more special one...
見れるかもしれない そしてね
...might make an appearance!
さっきも言いました この放送では
Also, as I mentioned earlier, during this broadcast...
ちょっとまだ脱げないかな って言ってたものがありますよね
...there's something we can't take off yet, right?
いろんな撮影会しましょう！
Let's take lots of photos!
というわけで ここまで付き合ってくれてありがとう！あんきもバイバーイ！
Thank you for joining us today! Bye-bye, Ankimou!
サングラス似合ってたぞ！
Those sunglasses looked great on you!
みんな吸い込まれていく
Everyone is getting sucked in.
はい というわけでね
Yes, and with that...
皆さんいかがだったでしょうか？
...how did everyone like it?
こんなにね いつもの情報の洪水が起こっていると思うんですが
I know it was a huge flood of information as usual,
ぜひぜひ皆さんあとで見ていただけたら嬉しいです
but I hope you'll check it all out later.
最後はですね これだけ決意のソラへとおい 歌わないのはどうかなと思いますので
Lastly, since I've talked so much about "Ketsui no Sora e," it wouldn't be right not to sing it,
新曲で締めたいと思います！
so I'd like to end the show with my new song!
それでは聴いてください 決意のソラへ！
Now, please listen: "Ketsui no Sora e"!
一度きりの 私の物語には
In my one and only story...
運命を超えて 煌めくんだ
...I will shine beyond destiny!
行こう
Let's go!
みんな本日ありがとうございました！とっても楽しかったー！
Thank you so much for today, everyone! I had so much fun!
ねえ 私より私のことを
Hey, you know me even better...
分かってくれる キミの存在が
...than I know myself. Your presence...
臆病で 泣き虫な心に
...cast a spell called courage...
勇気と言う 魔法をかけたの
...onto my cowardly, crybaby heart.
チクタク 時計の針だけが進む
Tick-tock, only the hands of the clock move forward.
立ち止まってちゃダメだ
I must not stand still.
ソラ 転び八起きがお決まりでしょう
Look up, falling down seven times and getting up eight is the rule, right?
一つ一つ 重ねてきた
One by one, we've built them up...
大切なアルバムをめくるように
...like flipping through a precious album.
一つ一つ 叶えてきた今日まで
One by one, we've made our dreams come true.
その全てに キミがいてくれた
You were there with me through all of it.
終わりのない夢を
This endless dream...
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 追いかけて行こう
...let's keep chasing it forever and ever!
行こう
Let's go!
あんきもとのコラボドリームも果たしたそうで ありがとうございます！
We also fulfilled our collab dream with Ankimou, thank you so much!
ねえ ここで笑い合えることが
Hey, being able to laugh together here...
何よりも大事な真実
...is a truth more important than anything else.
チクタク イタズラなハートが痛む
Tick-tock, my mischievous heart aches.
空回り 空回り
Spinning my wheels, spinning my wheels...
思考回路フル回転で
...with my mind running at full speed.
よーいどん
Ready, set, go!
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights I cried and cried...
大切な人生のストーリーだから
...are an important part of my life's story.
夢を
Dreams...
夢で終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want them to end as just dreams!
まだ見ぬ景色を
The scenery we've yet to see...
見に行こうよ
...let's go see it together!
もっと もっと
More and more!
輝いて
Shine brighter!
高く 高く
Higher and higher!
飛び立とう
Let's take flight,
奇跡さえも超えて
even surpassing miracles!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
皆さん、たくさんのコメント、ありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for all the comments!
一つ一つ
One by one,
重ねてきた
we've piled them up.
未来地図のページを
Just like turning the pages...
めくるように
...of our map to the future.
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights when I cried and cried,
大切な人生のストーリーだから
are part of my precious life story.
夢を
Dreams...
夢で終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want them to end as just dreams!
まだ見ぬ景色を
The scenery we've yet to see...
見に行こうよ
...let's go see it together!
終わりのない歌を
An endless song...
君に 君に 君へと届け
Let it reach you, you, and only you!
ずっと ずっと 誓うの
I will vow forever and ever,
決意のソラへ
toward the sky of determination.
行こう！
Let's go!
本当にみんなのおかげで、最高の誕生日になりました！
Thanks to everyone, this has truly been the best birthday ever!
みんなのこと大好きだよ！
I love you all so much!
アフターライブも来てね！
Come to the after-live too!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026 / 告知あり
[Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026 / Announcement Included]